介意我快速打掃一下嗎
Mind if i do a quick mop?
你好大聲
You're shouting.
什麽
What?
- 我能稍後再來 - 不用 沒事
-I can come back later. -No, it's fine.
什麽都別碰就行
Just don't touch anything.
"Just don't touch anything."
賤人
Dickbreath.
你想要一粒爽口糖?
You want a tic tac?
好吧 我就當是不要
All right. I'll take that as a no.
拜託
Oh. Come on.
你到底怎麽了 老兄
What the hell happened to you, dude?
多德?多德是什麽鳥名字
Dod? What the fuck kind of name is dod?
進去 進去
Go, go, go, go, go.
拜託
Come on!
不 不 不 重開 重開
No! Oh, no, no, no. Reset, reset.
見鬼 見鬼
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
多德 拜託
Dod! Come on!
清除 接受 接你媽
Clear! Accept! Accept the motherfucker!
見鬼 好吧
Shit. Okay. All right.
做心肺復蘇吧 對
I'll do cpr. Yeah.
好了 塔基斯辣薯卷
All right! Some takis fuego.
拜託
Come on!
拜託 呼吸 老兄
Come on, breathe, dude!
見鬼 天呐
Oh, shit! Oh, hell, no.
好吧  來 多德
Okay. All right. All right. Come on, dod.
來 我們有這個呢
Come on. We got this.
拜託 多德
Please, come on, dod!
一千零一
One, one thousand!
一千零二
Two, one thousand!
不要 不要
No, no, no!
拜託
Come on.
你在逗我啊
You are kidding me.
糟糕
Oh, crap.
怎麽了
Why?
殭屍教戰守則
知道什麽比酷更酷嗎
You know  what's cooler than cool?
童子軍活動
Scouting!
開拍
Action!
你們好 夥計們 我是童子軍隊長羅傑斯
Hi, there, guys. My name is scout leader Rogers.
我在此向你們展示何謂童子軍 來...
And I'm here to show you what scouting is all about. Come...
童子軍是友誼的黏著劑
Being a scout is about  the bonds of friendship.
看看吧
Check it out!
這些童子軍在爭取弓與箭獎章
These scouts are on their way  to earning a bow  and arrow badge!
獎章是童子軍最高成就的象徵
Badges are the scouts'  highest symbol of achievement.
童子軍可以獲取各類獎章
Scouts can earn  all sorts of badges.
什麽比酷更酷
What's cooler than cool?
童子軍活動
Scouting!
好了 你是參加還是參加
All right, are you in or are you in?
嘿 聽著 每週五有免費餅乾
Hey, listen, there's free cookies every Friday.
我們在週六有團體歌頌
We do sing-alongs on Saturdays.
在大學申請上很亮眼的
It looks great on a college application!
我喜歡這例行悲劇
I love this tragic ritual.
總有人會報名的 夥計們
Someone's gonna sign up, guys!
我們得不斷嘗試
We have to keep trying!
奧基 在有人加入前 一頭獨角獸
Augie, a unicorn's gonna fly out of your ass
會從你屁股裏飛出來
before somebody joins.
卡特 注意言辭
Carter! Language.
他說的沒錯 沒人會報名
Yeah, he's right. Nobody's ever gonna sign up.
只是在浪費時間
It's just a waste of time.
你們缺乏信念 童子軍精神哪去了
Ye of little faith. Where's that scout spirit?
聽著 夥計們 我們不會就因爲坐在這
Look, guys, we're not gonna quit trying just because
毫無進展地失去了幾小時
we lost a couple hours sitting around on our butts
而放棄嘗試
with nothing to show for it.
我意思是 有些人用了一生的時間
I mean, some people spend their entire lives
都毫無進展
and have nothing to show for it.
好了
Well...
我想我們都知道今晚是奧基的特別之夜
I think we all know it's augie's special night.
經過多年的努力和奉獻
After years of hard work and dedication,
他將在今晚的露營
he will receive the highest honor of a scout,
得到童子軍的最高榮譽
the condor badge,
禿鷹獎章
in a ceremony at tonight's campout.
好了 我們來看下
Okay. Let's see.
負責公厠的是卡特
Latrine duty: Carter.
不行 總是我挖便坑
No! No, no, no, no. I always dig the shitter.
那叫公厠 不叫便坑
It's called a latrine, not a shitter.
好了 本 你負責香腸
All right, Ben, you're on wiener duty.
夠了
That's enough.
卡特 沒人這樣吃熱狗
Carter, nobody eats a hot dog like this.
好了 本 不如你帶我們說童子軍誓詞吧
All right. Ben, why don't you lead us in the scout oath?
- 來啊 - 好吧
- Come on.  -All right.
我宣誓
This do I swear:
勇敢地活著
To live courageously,
力所能及地幫助他人
to help others when I can,
保衛我必須保衛的一切 願上帝助我
defend what I must, so help me god.
童子軍萬歲
Scouts forever!
Scouts forever.
童子軍萬歲
萬歲
Forever!
本 我們得告訴奧基
Ben, we have to tell augie.
- 我知道 我知道 - 我們要退出童子軍
- I know. I know. - We're ditching scouts.
我們會告訴他的
Yeah, we'll tell him.
我們說這事有一年多了
We've been talking about it for over a year.
我知道 我們得找一個正確的時機
I know. We just have to find the right time.
好吧 那就今晚
Okay, we'll do it tonight, then.
不行 今晚不能告訴他 他要領取他的禿鷹獎章啊
No, we can't tell him tonight. He's getting his condor badge.
他加入童子軍以來就一直在爲此努力
He's been working toward this ever since he joined scouts.
你知道這對他意義重大
You know how much it means to him.
尤其是在他爸沒法到場的情況下
Especially since his dad can't be there.
兩年了 本
It's been two years, Ben.
我們不能只是因爲覺得對不起他而留在童子軍
We can't just stay in scouts because we feel sorry for him.
拜託 我們留在童子軍不只是因爲這個原因
Come on, that's not the only reason we're staying in scouts.
拜託 你也得到了樂趣
Come on, you've had fun.
得到了樂趣 好嗎 表示已經過去了
Had fun, okay? Past tense. Had.
而我現在準備向前看 我意思是 你知道
And now I am ready to move on. I mean, you realize
明年是高三了
it's gonna be junior year next year.
你懂我意思 對嗎
I mean, you know what that means, right?
我們要開始考慮大學了
We start thinking about college.
我們要開始考慮女人 本
We start thinking about pussy, Ben!
拜託 高三是所有姑娘變浪女的時候
Come on. Junior year is when all the girls become sluts.
- 真的? - 沒錯
- Oh, really? -  Yes.
童子軍制服要是還被我們穿著
And if we're sitting here in these scout uniforms,
就會變成男版貞操帶 本
it's gonna be the male version of a chastity belt, Ben.
見鬼
Oh, shit. Shit.
那他媽是什麽
What the fuck was that?
真見鬼  天呐
Holy shit. Oh, my god.
見鬼
Oh, shit.
老兄 我被嚇出屎了
Dude, that scared the shit out of me.
我也是
Yeah, me, too.
不是 是真的有點屎出來了
No, like, literally, a little shit came out.
老兄 停下
Dude, stop.
天呐 你撞死了斑比
Jesus Christ. You hood-fucked Bambi.
我不是故意的 這不是我的錯 卡特
I didn't mean to! It wasn't my fault, Carter!
它就站在那兒
It was just standing there!
見鬼
Oh, shit.
該死的
Oh. Damn it.
好極了 太好了
Great. Just awesome.
那備胎給你單車用還汽車用的?
Is that a spare for your bike or the car?
見鬼 我爸一定會很生氣
Shit. My dad's gonna be so pissed.
卡特 其他車輪螺母呢
Carter, where are the other lug nuts?
我怎麽知道 我一直坐在這 什麽都沒幹
How should I know? I've been sitting here doing nothing.
是啊 我注意到了
Yeah. I noticed.
老兄 那是我姐
Oh. Dude, that's my sister.
肯達爾 肯達爾
Kendall! Kendall!
嘿
Hey!
Hey.
你能幫幫我們嗎
Can you help us?
接球
Catch!
- 傑夫 - 怎麽了
- Jeff! - What?
我說了 接球
I said, "catch."
我以爲他能接住
I thought he had it.
- 抱歉 兄弟 我的錯 - 是的
- Sorry, bro. It's my bad. - Yeah.
你們沒事吧 我是說 出什麽事了
Are you guys okay? I mean, what happened?
我們撞了一頭白尾鹿 它很大
We hit a white-tailed deer. It was huge.
是啊 我們剛開著車 然後就嘣的一聲
Yeah. We were just driving, and then it was like, boom!
你們撞了頭鹿?很棒啊
You guys hit a deer? That's awesome.
沒有 並不棒 你在開玩笑嗎
Nope, not awesome. Are you kidding?
沒什麽棒的 看看我的車
Nothing awesome about it. Look at my car.
還好嗎 克洛伊
What's up, Chloe?
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey... - Hey.
- 卡特 - 卡特
- Carter. - Carter!
沒錯 西班牙語課我坐在你後面
Yeah. I sit behind you in Spanish class.
我覺得你們穿的
So, I'm really down with this
這身小童子軍制服
whole little scout uniform you guys got going.
還有這些小補丁都很不錯
All these little patches and stuff.
實際上 本和卡特好像
Actually, Ben and Carter have been
從六歲起就是童子軍了 對嗎
scouts together since, what, you were like six, right?
- 是啊 很久了 - 很棒 兄弟
- Yeah, yeah. A long time. - That's awesome, man.
本就像我弟弟
Ben's like my little brother.
是啊 那就是我 本弟弟
Yep. That's me. Little brother Ben.
嘿 傑夫
Hey, Jeff!
好了 對你的臉我再次抱歉
All right, well. Sorry about that face again.
嘿 今晚你去派對嗎
Hey, are you going to the party tonight?
怎麽了
What's up?
吹簫狂婊 你好嗎
Aber-blow-me and bitch, man. What's up?
真會造詞
Always coming up with good ones.
聽著 我剛在這和卡福聊天
Listen, I was just talking to carver here, and...
是卡特
Carter.
- 我想到了一個很棒的主意 - 真的?
I came up with a great idea. Really?
說說 什麽主意
Hit me. What do we have?
招募怎麽樣了
How'd recruiting go?
老樣子 沒人參加
Oh, the usual. Yeah, no one joined.
我想當下只是個大笑話而已
I think it's just a big joke at this point.
並不是笑話
It's not a joke.
我覺得你們堅持做童子軍很酷
I think it's really cool you guys have stuck with scouts.
有一天你們會回顧這事
One day you're gonna look back on this
你們會很高興自己這麽做了
and you're gonna be really happy you did it.
好吧 謝謝
Okay. Thanks.
看樣子那頭鹿比你的車厲害
Looks like the deer made out better than your car.
是啊 等等 什麽 什麽意思
Yeah. Wait, what? What do you mean?
它哪去了
Well, where is it?
就在那邊
It's right over there.
天呐 天呐 老兄
Holy shit! Holy shit, man!
混蛋 你有病啊
You dick. What's wrong with you?
老兄 你絕不會信這事
Dude. Dude, okay. You're never gonna believe what happened.
嘿 你們確定不用搭車?
Hey, you sure you guys don't need a ride?
不用 我們沒事
No, we're good.
今晚見 小夥子們
See you boys tonight.
嘿 今晚見 老兄
Hey! See you tonight, man!
好嗎 好嗎
All right? All right?
再見 克洛伊 再見
Bye, Chloe! Bye!
你在說什麽今晚
What are you talking about, tonight?
老兄 你永遠猜不到是什麽事
Dude, you are never going to guess what happened.
我們被邀去秘密高四派對 老兄 看
We got invited to the secret senior party, man. Look.
誰在乎啊 看啊 鹿不見了 鹿呢
Who cares? Look, the deer is gone. What about the deer?
老兄 去他媽的鹿
Dude, fuck deers, man!
我們要去神秘派對 老兄 快來
We are going to the secret party, man! Come on!
我要上克洛伊
I'm gonna fuck Chloe.
本 快來 這事千載難逢的機會
Ben, come on. This is the chance of a lifetime.
好吧 我是說別假裝你不想去
Okay. I mean, quit acting like you don't want to go.
我當然想去 我想去
Of course i want to go. I do.
但晚上是奧基的重要之夜 他要領取他的禿鷹獎章
But it's augie's big night. He's getting his condor badge.
我們不能錯過他的典禮 不然他永遠不會原諒我們
We can't miss the ceremony or he'd never forgive us.
好吧 聽我說
Okay, look, hear me out.
我們去露營
We go to the campout,
等奧基和羅傑斯睡著了
and when augie and Rogers fall asleep,
我們溜出去 然後去派對
we will sneak out and go to the party.
卡特
Carter...
我們黎明前回來
We'll be back before dawn,
就像從沒離開過一樣
it'll be like we never even left.
怎麽說呢 只是聽上去...
I don't know. It just sounds...
本
Ben.
這會是我們一生中最棒的一晚
This could be the night of our lives.
求你了
Please.
好吧 我想我們能試試
All right. I mean, i guess we could try.
- 我愛你 - 好吧
- I love you. - Okay.
你太好了 謝謝
You're amazing. Thank you!
哇哦 幹嘛呢
Whoa! What the hell?
嗨 菲爾德夫人 嗨
Hi, Mrs. fielder. Hi.
你的垃圾桶又檔了我的車道
Your garbage cans were blocking my driveway again.
我不得不親自搬開它們
Had to move them myself,
這對腰間盤突出的人來說並不容易
which is no easy task with a herniated disk.
好吧 太好了
Okay, great.
叫你爸把他的垃圾管管好
You tell your father to keep his trash on his side of the property.
好的 我們會管好的 菲爾德夫人 謝謝了
Okay, we'll do that, Mrs. fielder. Thank you.
好了 謝謝 你能挪一下嗎
All right, thanks. Yep. Can you just move right there?
謝謝 再見
Thank you. Bye!
天啊
Jesus Christ.
老巫婆 好了 謝謝了
You old hag! Okay. Thank you.
她好煩人
She is so annoying.
天呐 你能想像住她隔壁是什麽感覺嗎
Oh, my god. Can you imagine living next to that?
天啊 老兄 她有多少只貓啊
Oh, my god. Dude, how many cats does she have?
老兄 誰知道啊 她大概在陰部抹了碎肉
Dude, who knows. She probably rubs fancy feast on her cooch
再讓它們舔
and lets them all go to town.
什麽
What?
五點半在這碰頭 接著我們去露營
Meet me here at 5:30 and then we'll go to camp womp womp.
然後我們去派對 好嗎
Then we'll go to the party. All right?
- 好嗎 - 好 好
All right? All right. All right.
回見 老兄
See you soon, man.
好的 再見
All right. See ya.
啊 有垃圾
Oh, litterbugs.
拜託
Come on.
維生素?
Biotine?
你怎麽來這的
How'd you get way out here?
皮特•莫瑞斯 誰撿到歸誰
Well, Peter Morris, finders keepers.
有人嗎
Hello?
你有病啊
What's wrong with you?
混蛋
You a-wipe!
賤貨 所有髒話都給你
C-word! All the other words!
王八蛋
Oh, doodle!
那可是我的幸運刀
That's my lucky knife!
童子軍隊長羅傑斯教你做鹿
Teach you to mess with scout leader Rogers!
所以我們這樣走進去就行?
So we're just gonna walk in there like this?
不用身份證 只要買些啤酒?
No I.D.'S, just buy some beer?
給我張20美元 白癡 快
Just give me the $20, fool. Come on.
掏錢
Cough it up.
快點 快
Any day now. Come on.
別急 這是尼龍搭扣 一秒就好
Hang on. It's velcro. It takes a second.
看我的
Watch a pro.
- 嗨 先生 今天過得如何 - 嘿 寶貝
- Hi, sir. How are you today? - Hey, baby.
太好了 好棒的計劃 卡特
Oh, nice. Great plan, Carter.
把錢給醉酒流浪漢 真行得通
Just give the money to a drunk bum. That'll work.
太好了
Yeah!
就買便宜的
Just the cheap stuff.
你看見性感警官了嗎
Did you see officer hottie?
沒 我就顧著看你怎麽丟掉20美元
No. I was too busy watching you lose 20 bucks.
好吧 我給了他具體說明
Okay, I gave him very specific instructions.
他會給我們買兩箱六瓶裝
He's gonna buy us a couple of six packs,
找零歸他
and he can keep the change.
天啊
Jesus.
哇哦
Whoa.
天啊 老兄 是她
Holy shit, dude. That's her.
什麽 誰
What? Who?
蒂尼絲什麽的
It's Denise what's-her-face.
她在我們高中讀過
She went to our high school.
幾年前輟學了
She dropped out a couple years ago.
現在她是個脫衣舞女
Now she's a stripper.
你怎麽知道
How do you even know that?
她是一個傳奇
She's a legend.
她怎麽了
What happened to her?
他媽的他在搞什麽 天呐
What the fuck is he... Jesus Christ.
先生
Sir!
我不會給這些東西付錢
I'm not paying for these items.
先生
Sir?
見鬼
Shit!
沒事 我自己來 說真的 我自己來
It's okay. I got it. Seriously, I got it.
該死的破包
Fucking ghetto-ass bag.
這樣
Here.
你在幹嘛
What are you doing?
打了個單編結
It's a sheet bend knot.
不可能會脫結
It's impossible to break.
真心靈手巧
You're pretty handy.
謝謝
Thanks.
出去
Get out.
- 腿不錯 - 啊?
- Nice legs. - Huh?
變裝派對?
Costume party?
不是 我...
Oh, no, I'm...
我是名童子軍
I'm a scout.
真童子軍?
Like an actual scout?
是啊 今晚我們有一次露營
Yeah, well. We got a campout tonight.
你在街對面工作?
So you work across the street?
對 炫吧?
Yep. Glamorous, huh?
是啊 我意思是我從沒進去過
Yeah. I mean, I've never been in,
但聽說不錯
but I hear it's nice.
在尖叫點評上大受好評
It's got a good yelp review.
- 怎麽了 - 沒什麽
- What? - Nothing.
你只是...你很可愛
You're just... You're really cute.
謝謝
Thanks.
快點 卡特
Come on, Carter.
你沒叫那人買啤酒吧
Please tell me you did not ask that guy to buy you beer.
沒 是他的主意
No, it was his idea.
你去哪...
Where are you...
20美元還我
I need my $20 back.
- 我要怎麽對付那個壞人 - 這不全是你的
- How am I gonna fight the bad guy? - It's not all yours.
你好髒 看看多髒啊...
You're dirty. Look how dirty...
給你
Here.
謝謝
Thank you.
謝謝 請
Thank you. Here.
天啊 謝謝了
Oh, my god. Thank you.
你是世界上最好的人 謝謝
You're the most amazing person ever. Thank you.
沒錯 謝謝
Yeah. Thanks.
沒事 謝謝幫忙 跑腿
It's cool. And thanks for the help, legs.
應該的
Yeah.
老兄 剛才什麽情況
Dude, what the fuck was that?
天呐
Oh, my god.
我要天天舔她的鹹濕部位
I would tongue-pound her salty walrus any day of the week.
見鬼
Oh, shit.
- 他在盯著我們 - 走吧
- He's staring at us. - Go.
老兄 我想你跟我說過肯達爾和那個傑夫分了
Dude, I thought you said that Kendall broke up with that Jeff guy.
老兄 我是以爲分了
Dude, i thought so too.
他們一會兒在一起
It's like, one moment, they're together
一會兒又像是分手了
and the next moment, they're broken up.
所以他是個混蛋
So he's a dick.
毫無疑問...
It's like no doubt...
嘿 夥計們
Hey, guys!
嘿 你好嗎
Hey, what's up?
對了 營地搭建了一半了
All right. Campsite is halfway set up.
- 不錯 - 很棒
- Nice. - Great.
- 好啊 - 好
- What's up? - What's up?
好
What's up?
太慢了 太慢了 老兄
Oh! Too slow. Too slow, buddy.
童子軍隊長羅傑斯呢
Where's scout leader Rogers?
他本該在這幫我搭建的
He was supposed to be here to help me set up,
但到現在他還沒出現
but so far he's a no-show.
奇怪 他從不遲到
That's weird. He's never late.
沒錯 或許他退出童子軍了
Yeah. Maybe he quit scouts.
退出童子軍?是啊 沒錯
Quit scouts? Yeah, right.
真是可笑至極
That's hysterical!
想知道我怎麽想的嗎 我覺得這是一次考驗
Want to know what I think it is? I think it's a test.
一次考驗?
A test?
是啊 今天我要領取我的禿鷹獎章
Well, yeah. I'm getting my condor badge today.
我得證明我做好了準備
I have to prove that I'm ready.
對了 看下這個
Yeah, and check this out.
我在爲動物研究獎章做飲食記錄
I'm charting diets for the animal study badge
然後正好走進了這東西裏
and I walked right into that.
- 這是什麽 - 鹿屎
- What is this? - It's deer scat.
老兄 搞什麽啊
Oh, dude! What the fuck, man?
卡特 我需要那東西啊
Carter! I needed that!
你需要那東西?那是屎啊 奧基
You needed that? It's shit, augie!
沒人需要屎
No one needs shit!
我需要 我找了一整周
I need it! I've been looking all week for it.
天呐 這將是漫長的一夜
Oh, god. It's gonna be a long night.
穿過去 一進一出
Just feeding it through, in and out.
好爽
Oh, yeah.
搞定
There you go.
- 幹得好 夥計 - 我搞定了
- Good job, bud. - I did it!
搞什麽啊 兄弟 是你的屁股嗎
What the fuck, man? Was that your ass?
豆子?香腸?
Beans? Weenies?
爲什麽我們總得吃福利食品
Why do we always have to eat welfare food?
因爲我們在露營 卡特 你想吃什麽
Because we're camping, Carter. What do you want?
廚藝滿滿的 不會讓我每五秒
Something artisan. Something that doesn't make me
就放屁的
fart every five seconds.
閉嘴 別那麽賤
Shut up. Quit being such a bitch.
奧基 奧基
Augie? Augie?
嘿 奧基
Hey, augie!
用我打火機
Use my lighter.
用打火機我就得不到
I'm not gonna get my fire making badge
生火獎章了 卡特
using a lighter, Carter.
- 就用吧 - 不行
- Just use it. - No!
- 爲什麽 - 因爲所以
- Why? - 'Cause!
奧基 就用吧 你能下次爭取
Augie, just use it. You can get it next time.
什麽情況 到底爲什麽我收不到信號
What the fuck? Why the hell can't I get service?
卡特 我們在樹林裏
Carter, we're in the woods.
我在這上面總收得到啊
I always get service up here.
卡特 也許大自然母親想要你
Maybe mother nature wants you
把手機放一邊 再融入當下
to put the phone away, Carter, and be in the moment.
大自然母親這麽想的嗎
Oh, is that what mother nature wants?
也許大自然母親想這樣
Maybe mother nature wants this.
正中靶心 兄弟
Fucking bull's-eye, man!
你是個蠢貨 卡特
You're an asshead, Carter.
等下 別 別 別 別拿下來
Wait! No, no, no, no! Don't take it off.
等下
Here we go. Wait. Hold still.
別動 準備好沒 說棉花糖
Hold still. Ready? Say, "marshmallow."
卡特吸驢蛋
Carter sucks donkey balls.
美美的
That's a thing of beauty.
你最好別上傳
You better not post that.
我絕對要上傳 它是我的傑作
I'm definitely posting that. It's my masterpiece.
好了 馬上回來 夥計們 我得撒尿
All right. Brb, guys. I got to pee.
倉鴞?
Barn owl?
我覺得是斑點貓頭鷹
I think it's a spotted owl.
是啊 你大概是對的
Yeah, you're probably right.
猜猜我上來時發現了什麽
Guess what I found when I was hiking up here?
那棵被我們刻上我們首字母的樹
I found the tree we carved our initials into.
- 不會吧 - 真的
- No way! - Yeah.
- 真的? - 沒錯
- Really? - Yeah.
哇哦 那好像是七年前的事了
Wow. That was like seven years ago.
我知道 不可思議吧
I know. Crazy, right?
那天和卡特在拉屎時
Oh. That was the same day Carter sat on the cactus
坐到仙人掌上是同一天 對嗎
when he was taking a shit, right?
然後你爸不得不挑掉那些刺
And your dad had to pick out the needles.
是啊
Yeah.
奧基 我知道我們不怎麽聊你爸
Augie, I know we don't talk about your dad much,
但你想的話也沒關係
but it's okay if you want to.
要知道 我只是不想掃興
I just don't want to be a downer, you know.
別這樣 奧基 你不會掃興的
Come on, augie, you're not being a downer.
他是你爸
He was your dad.
你能談談他
You can talk about him.
謝了 本
Thanks, Ben.
沒事 應該的
Yeah. Of course.
童子軍萬歲?
Scouts forever?
當然 童子軍萬歲
Yeah. Scouts forever.
本 嘿
Ben. Hey.
來吧 本 我們走
Come on, Ben. Let's go.
卡特 我覺得這樣不太好
Carter, I don't know about this.
你能別杞人憂天了嗎
Will you stop crying about this?
走吧 快 動起來
Let's go. Come on, we're doing this.
走吧 來啊
Let's go. Come on.
快
Come on.
我們有打擾到嗎
Are we interrupting?
你們看上去好棒
You look amazing.
謝謝
Thank you.
嘿 你們看到我弟了嗎
Hey, have you guys seen my brother?
他本該已經到了
He should have been here by now.
沒看到 哪都沒他影子
No. I haven't seen him anywhere, no.
聽著 我肯定他很快會到這裏 好嗎
But look, I'm sure he'll be here any second. Okay?
老兄 奧基要是醒了而我們不在那怎麽辦
Dude. What if augie wakes up and we're not there?
他不會醒
He's not gonna wake up.
要是我們營地的楚巴卡是個該死的大腳怪
If Chewbacca was fucking bigfoot in our campsite,
他就不會醒
he'd still be asleep.
- 那是什麽 - 什麽
- What is that? - What?
看 看啊 他來過這裏
Look. Look, he was here.
好吧 所以他決定回家了
Okay. So, he decided to go back home.
他改主意了
He changed his mind.
不是 童子軍隊長羅傑斯
No, no, no. Scout leader Rogers
永遠不會離開他的幸運刀
would never leave his lucky knife.
我覺得有些不對勁
I think something's wrong.
老兄 我們有病啊 坐這裏聊這些
Dude, what's wrong is us sitting here talking about this.
老兄 看啊 看他的腳印
Dude, look. Look at his prints.
他拖著腳走路 像是跛了似的
His foot was dragging like he had a limp or something.
好吧 爲你凶殘的追蹤技術喝彩
Okay. Hurray for your mad tracking skills.
我們能...我們能走了嗎 行嗎
Can we just... Can we go? Please?
我就覺得他出了很嚴重的事
I just think something really bad happened to him.
- 又在說羅傑斯嗎 - 是啊
- Are we still talking about Rogers? - Yeah.
老兄 他坐在家裏穿得像多莉•帕頓
Dude, he is sitting at home dressed up like Dolly parton
唱著秀場樂 安心吧
singing show tunes. Relax.
糟糕
Oh, shit.
奧基 等下 奧基
Augie, wait! Augie!
奧基
Augie!
我以爲我們是摯友
I thought we were best friends.
我們是摯友
We are best friends.
- 我們正要回來 - 真的?
- We were coming back. - Really?
在派對之後吧
After your party?
你知道?
You know about that?
所有人都知道高四派對的事 卡特
Everybody knows about the senior party, Carter.
我這種窩囊廢都知道
Even a loser like me.
奧基 別那麽說
Augie, don't say that.
爲什麽 你們是這麽想的啊
Why not? It's what you guys think!
我們沒覺得你是窩囊廢
We don't think you're a loser.
本 就告訴他吧
Ben, just tell him.
卡特 不行
Carter, no.
是啊 告訴我 本
Yeah, tell me, Ben.
快 說啊
Come on! Say it!
我們要退出童子軍 奧基
We're quitting scouts, augie.
聽著 我們小時候 這挺有意思
Look, it was fun when we were kids.
但我們得長大 兄弟
But we have to grow up, man.
奧基 我們還要做摯友
Augie. We're still gonna be best friends.
去你們的派對吧
Go to your party.
奧基
Augie.
奧基 等等
Augie, wait!
奧基 別這樣
Augie, come on!
就讓他去吧 本
Just leave him, Ben.
怎麽回事 收音機怎麽了
What the fuck... What's wrong with the radio?
卡特 你發現了嗎
Carter, are you seeing this?
發現什麽
Seeing what?
看啊 鎮上沒人了
Look. The town's deserted.
大家大概都睡了
Everyone's probably asleep.
在週五晚上?
On a Friday night?
說不清楚 感覺很怪
I don't know. Something just feels really weird.
嘿 就停那裏
Oh, hey. Pull over right here.
我等不及脫掉這愚蠢的制服了
I can't wait to get out of these stupid uniforms.
好了 我來看看這裏
All right. Let's see here.
我們就在這換?
We're just gonna change right here?
周圍沒人啊
Nobody's around.
牛仔褲 T恤
Let's see. Jeans. T-shirt.
避孕套 準備好了
Condoms. Good to go. Uh...
忘帶襪子了?確實忘了
Forget socks? Yes, I did.
- 天啊 - 這麽了
- Holy shitballs! - What?
老兄 看啊
Dude, look.
什麽
What?
保安 他不在
The bouncer, he's gone!
卡特 有人砸了門
Carter, someone smashed the door.
我們該溜進去
We should sneak in.
- 我們溜進去 快 溜進去 - 那不合法
- Let's sneak in. Come on. Let's do it. - That's illegal.
卡特 我們不能進去
Carter, we can't go in there!
來啊
Come on!
我們不能進去 我們未成年
We can't go in there. We're minors.
這是千載難逢的機會 管它呢
It's the chance of a lifetime. Who cares?
你搞什麽啊
What are you doing?
會很棒的
It's gonna be awesome!
天呐 等下 等下 等下
Oh, my god. Wait, wait, wait.
好了 沒問題 來吧 進去吧
Okay, it's clear. Come on. Let's do it.
天啊
Sweet Jesus.
就是這樣 本
This is it, Ben.
我們進來了
We've made it.
我們在女人堆裏了
We're at the epicenter of pussy.
見鬼 我得去自動取款機那取點現金
Oh, shit. I got to go to the atm, get some cash.
你給我們找個位置
You find us a spot.
是啊 沒人在這
Yeah. That shouldn't be too hard
應該不會太難找
since there's, like, nobody here.
嘿
Hey!
我朋友帶我來這的 他在取錢
My friend brought me here. He's getting money.
我有女朋友 算有吧
I have a girlfriend, sort of.
媽媽 別擔心 爸爸來了
Don't worry, mommy, daddy's here!
老兄 爽死了
Dude, this is fucking awesome!
老兄 她有些不對勁
Dude, something's wrong with her.
看她胸口 那上面都是什麽
Look at her chest. What's all over her?
沒事 那是化的妝 是叢林風
No, no. That's makeup, dummy. It's a jungle theme.
哇哦
Oh, wow.
太誘人了
This is so hot.
天啊
Oh, my god.
Oh, my god!
快跑 快跑
Run! Quick, run!
門 去門那
Door, door, door, door!
起來 起來 起來
Get up! Get up! Get up!
- 卡特 - 本 本
- Carter! - Ben? Ben.
這他媽什麽情況
What the fuck is going on?
不知道 他們在試圖殺我們
I don't know! They're trying to kill us!
- 我只是想看些咪咪啊 - 我知道
I just wanted to see some titties! I know!
等下 你是那個脫衣舞女
Wait. You're the stripper.
是鶏尾酒女招待
Cocktail waitress.
童子軍隊長羅傑斯
Scout leader Rogers?
童子軍隊長羅傑斯 你在家嗎
Scout leader Rogers, are you home?
有人嗎
Hello?
天啊
Holy cow.
給我冷靜
Calm the fuck down!
冷靜?你瘋了嗎 我們差點在裏面被殺
Calm down? Are you crazy? We almost got killed in there!
- 那是你的車嗎 - 能麻煩你告訴我們
- Is that your ride? - Can you please just tell us
我現在真的得洗把臉
I really need to wash up my face right now!
鑰匙 拿來
Keys, now!
不行 除非你告訴我們怎麽回事
No! Not until you tell us what's happening.
誰有濕巾
Anybody got a wet nap?
你他媽認爲是怎麽回事
What the fuck do you think is happening?
大家在人吃人
Everyone's eating each other!
- 等下 像是... - 沒錯
-Wait, like a... -Yes, like that!
不可能
That's not possible.
我想是可能的 本
I think it's possible, Ben.
一個死了的脫衣舞女試圖吃我臉
A dead stripper just tried to eat my face!
見鬼
Oh, shit!
該死 見鬼
Oh, fuck. Oh, shit.
朝它開槍 開槍
Just shoot it! Shoot it!
沒錯 是僵屍
Yep. Zombie.
還有問題嗎
Any more questions?
開車 老兄 開車 快
Drive, dude, go! Come on!
你去哪 搞什麽啊
Where are you going? What the fuck?
見鬼
Oh, shit!
卡特 去拿輪胎
Carter, get the tire!
拿到了
I got it.
夥計們 快點 他們越來越他媽靠近了
Guys, hurry up! They're getting pretty fucking close!
- 快啊 - 我在儘量快了
- Come on! - I'm going as fast as I can.
去找該死的車輪螺母
Find the fucking lug nuts.
該死
Fuck.
說真的 給我快點
Seriously, hurry the fuck up!
找到了 給 給
I got them! Here. Here.
安上去
Put it on!
好的 很好 裝上 裝上
Okay. Good. Put it on! Put it on!
搞定了
I got it!
見鬼
Oh, shit!
你媽的一定是在逗我
You got to be fucking kidding me.
開車 開車
Go! Go! Go!
童子軍隊長羅傑斯 今晚怎麽回事
Scout leader Rogers! What happened tonight?
我們擔心你呢
We were worried about you.
我知道那不禮貌 很抱歉 我不得不用你家厠所
I know. It's bad. I'm so sorry. I had to use your bathroom.
我想是因爲豆子
I think it was the beans.
和棉花糖的緣故
And the marshmallows.
我試了噴霧 就是散不去那味
I tried spraying. It just lingers.
童子軍隊長羅傑斯 拜託 別這樣
Scout leader Rogers! Please!Stop!
我想你對某種東西産生了嚴重過敏
I think you're having a bad allergic reaction to something!
我們得帶你看醫生
We need to get you to a doctor!
所有撤離巴士已經離開
"All evacuation buses have departed.
經由1號國道
"Proceed north on route 1
前往17號英里標記處的安檢站
"to the security checkpoint at mile marker 17."
見鬼 鎮上的人被撤離了
Oh, shit. They evacuated the town.
真是太好了
That's great.
我錯過了派對 也沒見著克洛伊
I missed the party, and I missed Chloe,
- 而我現在要死了 - 夥計們
- and now I'm gonna die. - Guys.
卡特 冷靜 我們得想想
Carter, calm down! We need to figure out
- 怎麽辦 - 夥計們
- what we're gonna do. - Guys!
快走
Come on.
快 快 快走
Go, go, go!
- 卡特 鎖門 - 我他媽是想鎖啊 老兄
- Carter, lock it! - I'm trying to fuckin' lock it, man!
鎖不住啊
It's not working.
- 快啊 - 我在試
- Come on! - I'm trying!
走開
Move!
快走
Come on!
卡特 去拿斧頭
Carter, get the axe!
快走 快走
Go, go, go.
他們來了
They're coming!
真他媽太好了 現在怎麽辦
This is fucking awesome! Now what?
我真抱歉放火燒你 童子軍隊長羅傑斯
I'm really sorry i set you on fire, scout leader Rogers.
但願傷得沒看起來那麽嚴重
But hopefully, it's not as bad as it looks.
我打了雙反手收尾結
I used a double overhand stopper knot.
很難掙脫 對嗎
It's hard to get out of, right?
好的 好吧
Okay. All right.
好了 我馬上回來
Okay, now. I'll be right back.
好好待著
Just stay there.
夥計 搞什麽啊
Dude, what the fuck?
你們沒吃夠嗎 天呐
Haven't you had enough to eat? Jesus.
卡特 別惹怒他們
Carter, stop agitating them.
怎麽了 我要張新的檔案照
What? I need a new profile pic.
那麽 你覺得派對的人都被他們撤離了嗎
So, do you think they evacuated everyone at the party?
當然 他們必須那麽做
Yeah, of course. They had to.
至少我們知道我們父母沒事
At least we know our parents are okay.
- 是啊 - 他們在哪
- Yeah. - Where are they?
他們去了某個蹩腳的心靈瑜伽靜修處
They went to some lame spiritual yoga retreat.
我寧願待在這裏
Ugh. I think I'd rather be in here.
但願奧基沒事
I hope augie's okay.
- 奧基是誰 - 他是我們的摯友
Who's augie? He's our best friend.
現在是前任摯友了
Well, ex-best friend now.
爲什麽是前任
Why ex?
我們因爲派對而甩開了他
Because we ditched him for a party.
本 我們是要回去的
Ben, we were gonna go back.
無所謂了 卡特 我們甩開了他 我們不上路
Whatever, Carter. We ditched him. We're bad friends.
你們爲什麽不帶上他
Why didn't you guys just take him with you?
你不認識奧基
You don't know augie.
- 怎麽 - 他只是與衆不同
- What? - He's just different.
大怪胎?
Big geek?
他收集鹿屎 還編籃子
He collects deer shit and weaves baskets.
知道嗎 你想像下
Okay? You do the math.
好吧
Okay.
給個忠告
Word of advice,
在高中追求派對和流行?
chasing parties and popularity in high school?
完全沒用
It's a total dead end.
對於以後是無關緊要的
None of that shit will matter later.
相信我 我清楚
Trust me. I know.
你說的沒錯 但你不是在高中輟學了嗎
You're right, but didn't you, like, drop out of high school?
- 沒有 我拿到了同等學歷證 - 怎麽會
- No, I got my ged. - Why?
不是所有人都像你不學無術
'Cause not everybody has a Lily-white life like you do.
好吧 天啊 你真不友好
Okay. God, you're so hostile.
三秒後我踹你屁股才叫不友好
No, hostile is three seconds from now when my foot's up your ass.
好啊 放馬過來
Okay, yeah. Try all you want,
但我屁股恰巧很緊
but I happen to have a very tight asshole.
我想我能幫你撐開
I think I could stretch it out for you.
那幫我潤滑潤滑 寶貝
Oh, well, then lube me up, baby.
卡特 我們現在玩個安靜遊戲 好嗎
Carter! We're gonna play the quiet game now, okay?
好吧 你們可以的
All right, you know what? Fine.
我受夠你們兩個了
I'm over both of you.
你很拿手啊
You're pretty good at that.
是啊 我想切削獎章總算派上用場了
Yeah, I guess that whittling badge finally paid off.
你呢
What about you?
我?
What about me?
你怎麽學會用那種霰彈槍的
How'd you learn to use a shotgun like that?
我前男友對槍很感興趣
My ex-boyfriend was really into guns.
他每週都要拉我去次靶場
He used to drag me to the firing range once a week.
那現在沒男友?
So, no boyfriend now?
我會儘量避免有
Not if I can help it.
爲什麽這麽說
Well, why do you say that?
怎麽說呢
I don't know.
這麽說吧 我對男人的品位很差
Let's just say, i have really shitty taste in guys.
我一個人最好不過了
I'm better off alone.
沒人如此
Nobody's better off alone.
好吧 我就是
Yeah, well, I am.
多麽美好的一刻
Aww, what a beautiful moment.
混蛋 好痛
Ow! Asshole, that hurt!
- 當然 就是要這效果 - 就是要這效果?
- Yeah, that was the point! - Oh, was that the point?
夥計們 噓
Guys! Shh!
聽見沒
Do you hear that?
那是 就醬跳?
Is that  crank that?
他們離開了
They're leaving.
我喜歡這首歌
I love this song!
德行
You would.
看 那邊
Look! Right there.
該死 但他們會回來
Fuck. But they're gonna come back.
怎麽辦
What are we gonna do?
- 避孕套 - 什麽
- Condoms! - What?
卡特 把你的避孕套給我 快
Carter, give me your condoms! Hurry!
給 拿好 打開 再綁一起
Here. Take them and open them and tie them together.
爲什麽這麽做
Why are we doing this?
- 照做就是 - 好的 好的
- Just do it! - Okay, okay.
一個打開了
Here's one.
塊 快
Come on, hurry!
好了 飛釣 真是天才
Here we go. Fly fishing. It's genius.
繼續 再過去點 看准了
Go on, just a little bit. Get it right up there.
好了 快
There you go. Come on.
你行的 快
You got it, come on.
幹得好 太好了
Good work. Yes! Yes!
別 別 別
No, no, no!
天啊
Jesus!
你們被捕了?
You got arrested?
沒 我們把自己關了進來
No, we locked ourselves in.
- 怎麽會 - 意外
- How? - It was an accident!
這位一定是奧基
This has to be augie.
奧基 去拿鑰匙
Augie, get the keys.
你把它們踢進了那邊的排水管裏
You kicked them into the drainpipe over there.
- 我夠不到 - 見鬼
- I can't reach it! - Shit!
見鬼 他們要回來了
Shit, they're coming back.
別急
Hold on.
什麽 難道我不知道你還有開鎖獎章?
What, is there a lockpicking badge I'm unaware of?
你怎麽會找到我們
How'd you find us?
循著背叛的惡臭
Followed the stench of betrayal.
奧基
Augie...
我看見了你的車 我想我得幫忙
I saw your car. I figured I'd help.
- 奧基 聽著 我真的... - 好了
- Augie, look, I'm really... - Got it!
快走 快走
Go, go, go!
關上門
Close the gate!
哦..
Oh...
我的...
...my...
天...
...god.
卡特 走啊
Carter, let's go!
- 快  - 好的
- Come on! - Okay!
天呐 我摸到了 我摸到了
Oh, god. I touched them! I touched them!
我覺得是假的
I don't think they were real.
該死 我的腳痛死我了
Fuck, my feet are killing me.
安檢站就幾英里遠
The security checkpoint's only a few miles away.
老兄 我餓了
Dude, I'm starving.
有人在被活吃 你還能想著吃的?
How can you even think of food when people are being eaten alive?
要知道 據說人吃上去像豬肉
You know, they say that humans taste like pork.
據誰說
"They"?
我猜是食人族
Cannibals, I guess.
老兄 我喜歡培根
Dude, I love bacon.
嘿 看啊
Hey, look.
或許鑰匙在裏面
Maybe the keys are inside.
天呐 又是這傢夥?
Jesus! This guy again?
誰去殺了他
Someone kill him!
卡特 我們不能一直到處殺人
Carter, we can't just keep going around killing people.
爲什麽
Why not?
因爲他是人啊
Because he's a human being!
好吧 等他把你的蛋蛋
Okay. We'll see how you feel
當街頭夾餅吃時 我們再看你怎麽說
when he's eating your nutsack like a street taco.
夥計們 他越來越靠近了
Um, guys, he's getting pretty close.
記得我們的野外安全研討課嗎
Remember our wilderness safety seminar?
什麽
What?
遭遇有敵意的生物時 務必發起恐嚇
When encountering a hostile creature, be sure to assert yourself cntranslatedbyemtee
防止動物靠近
in order to keep the animal at bay.
我...
Well, I...
那是僵屍 不是熊 蠢貨
That is a zombie, not a bear, dumbass.
夥計們 我想他在模仿我
Guys, I think he's mimicking me.
奧基 別亂來
Augie, quit messing around.
怎麽了
What?
小甜甜布蘭妮
寶貝 寶貝
Oh baby baby
我怎麽知道
How was I supposed to know
事情不對勁了
that something wasn't right here
奧基 你在幹嘛
Augie, what are you doing?
寶貝 寶貝
Oh baby baby
我不該讓你離開
I shouldn't have let you go
現在你無影無蹤
and now you're out of sight yea
讓我知道你想怎樣
Show me how you want it to be
你在幹嘛
What are you doing?
告訴我 寶貝 因爲我要現在知道 因爲我的孤寂
tell me baby cause I need to know now,oh because,my loneliness
在要我命
is killing me
而我
and I
我必須承認我仍相信...
I must confess I still believe...
好吧 是我剛嗑藥了
Okay. Did i just drop acid,
還是他們真在和一個僵屍唱小甜甜布蘭妮的歌
or are they really singing Britney Spears with a zombie?
...我失去理智 給我一個提示
...I lose my mind,give me a sign
寶貝 再熱戀我一次
hit me baby one more time.
你們人都齊了?
Is that all of you?
沒錯 到底發生了什麽
Yeah. What the hell's happening?
還不知道 某種病毒爆發了
Don't know yet. Some kind of viral outbreak.
疾控中心要求軍方封隔邊界
CDC ordered a military containment perimeter.
鎮上大部分人都被撤離了嗎
Is most of the town evacuated?
我們儘量撤離了多數人
As many as we could.
這東西爆發得又猛又快
This thing hit so hard and fast,
我們仍在嘗試遏制它
we're still trying to contain it.
派對的人呢 都被撤離了嗎
What about everyone at the party? Were they evacuated?
什麽派對
What party?
人都在哪
Well, where is everybody?
這裏沒人 一定搞錯了
Nobody's here. It must be a mistake.
丹頓大街1146號 沒錯啊
Yeah, 1146 dunton Avenue. This is it.
沒搞錯 卡特 傑夫發了假地址給你
It's not a mistake, Carter. Jeff sent you a fake address.
什麽
What?
卡特 這裏是垃圾處理廠
Carter, this is a waste plant.
懂嗎 這裏全是垃圾
You get it? It's full of shit.
混蛋 該死的
Motherfucker! God damn it!
不敢相信他居然發了我假地址
I can't believe he sent us a fucking fake address!
有什麽好驚訝的
Why does it surprise you?
你真以爲
I mean, did you actually think
他會邀請我們去真正的派對?
he was gonna invite us to a real party?
因果報應
Karma.
什麽
What?
- 沒什麽 - 說啊
- Nothing. - No, speak up.
我只是覺得有點小諷刺
Well, I just think it's a little ironic
要知道 現在你們都很生氣
that, you know, you're all upset now
因爲你們被甩開了
because you got ditched.
好吧 所以你是說我們活該咯
Oh, okay. So you're saying that we deserve it.
我們去了你那愚蠢的露營 老兄
We went to your stupid campout, dude.
你們騙了我
You lied to me.
三年來我們一直在騙你
We've been lying to you for the past three years!
- 卡特 - 參加每一次童子軍會議
- Carter! - Going to every scout meeting,
每一次蹩腳的野遊
every lame field trip.
穿著這些愚蠢的衣服
Wearing these stupid fucking clothes
所以大家都能取笑我們
so everybody can make fun of us.
卡特 夠了
Carter, that's enough!
本 這次你別遮遮掩掩
Ben, you're not hiding behind me this time.
告訴他
Tell him.
說說你說過多少次
Talk about how many times
你討厭童子軍 你受夠了
you said you hated scouts, how sick of it you were.
- 我從沒那麽說過 - 放屁
- I never said that. - Bullshit!
沒事
No, no, no. It's fine.
我想是時候全說出來了 對嗎
I guess it's time for it to all come out, right?
他六年級開始就喜歡肯達爾了
He's had a crush on Kendall since sixth grade.
- 那不是真的 - 是真的
- That is not true! - Yes, it is.
- 肯達爾?我姐肯達爾? - 嗯哼
- Kendall? As in my sister Kendall? - Mmm-hmm.
- 不是的 - 老兄 那真像亂倫
- No. - Dude, that's like incest.
沒有 我和她甚至不是親戚
No, it's not, I'm not even related to her.
那你確實喜歡她
So you do like her, then.
- 我不喜歡她 - 我跟你說了
- No, I don't like her! - Told you.
閉嘴
Shut up!
住手
Stop!
又吵?天啊
Again with this shit? Jesus.
你就不能聯繫誰嗎
Can't you just walkie someone?
嘿 你還好嗎
Hey, are you okay?
夥計們
Guys!
糟糕
Shit!
抓住他
Get him!
我他媽受夠僵屍了
I'm so fucking sick of zombies!
呀
Yikes.
我的媽呀
Wa-wa-wee-wa.
見鬼
Shit!
喂 有人在嗎
Hello! Is anybody there?
撤離完成
Evac complete.
沒有 我們還在這裏
No, no, no, no. We're still here!
我們有清理行動
We have  operation clean up.
開始空中轟炸 地點爲0300 重複 0300
Commence aerial bombing  of site at 0300.  Repeat, 0300.
- 什麽 - 完畢
- What? - Over.
不要啊 來人救援啊 喂 喂
No, somebody help! Hello! Hello!
請來人救援 喂
Somebody help, please! Hello!
可惡
Fuck!
他們兩小時後要炸了這鎮?
They're gonna bomb the town in two hours?
我們怎麽辦
What are we gonna do?
我們得去找肯達爾和其他人
We have to find Kendall and the others!
那是個秘密派對 他們在哪都有可能
It's a secret party. They could be anywhere.
見鬼
Shit.
我姐的日記
My sister's diary!
她把她生活中每一個無聊的細節都寫在那裏
She writes every last boring detail of her life in there.
我保證她寫了派對地點
I guarantee she wrote down where the party is.
那我們趕緊走啊
We better get fucking going, then.
好了 快走
Okay, now.
好了 來
All right, come on.
這裏面聞起來像頑皮吸管糖和內衣的氣味
It smells like pixy stix and hope in here.
你以前從沒進過姑娘房間 對嗎
You've never been in a girl's room before, have you?
- 不對 我... - 媽媽不算
Yeah, I... Mom doesn't count.
- 好吧... - 任何女性親戚都不算
- Well... - Any female relative doesn't count.
夥計們 能專注點嗎 日記在哪
Guys! Can we focus? Where's the diary?
她每週都換地方藏
She changes the hiding place, like, every week,
所以分頭找吧
so just spread out and start looking.
- 你找到了嗎 - 沒
- Did you find it? - Nope.
這裏什麽都沒
Nothing over here.
嘿
Hey.
你們聽見沒
Did you guys hear that?
聽見什麽
Hear what?
我覺得我聽到樓下有聲音
I think I heard something downstairs.
奧基 去看看
Augie, go check it out.
我一個人才不下去
I'm not going down there by myself.
- 和他去啊 - 爲什麽是我
- Go with him. - Why me?
搞不定再叫我 夥計
Call me when your balls drop, dude.
噓
Shh!
走路別踩那麽重
Don't walk so hard.
你的地板在咯吱咯吱
You have squeaky floors.
這是卡特姐姐？
This is Carter's sister?
是啊 肯達爾
Yeah. That's Kendall.
她顯然遺傳了良好基因
Well, she clearly won the genetic lottery.
是啊 我覺得她還可以
Yeah. She's okay. I guess.
夥計 她不只是還可以
Dude, she's more than okay.
你對此不用掩飾
You don't have to be all cool about it.
見鬼
Shit.
該死 來
Fuck. Come on.
那麽 你怎麽沒告訴她你喜歡她
So, how come you haven't told her you like her?
有什麽用
What's the point?
她絕不會喜歡我這樣的人
She's never gonna go for a guy like me.
她有男朋友
And she's got a boyfriend.
而且我要是碰了卡特的姐姐 他會殺了我
And Carter would kill me if I touched his sister.
好吧 聽著 這樣好了
Okay, look. Here's the deal.
也別誤會
And don't take this the wrong way,
但你得爺們兒些
but you have to man up.
我知道 但我不擅長
Yeah, but I suck at being that guy.
我那樣子不自信
I'm not assertive like that.
吻我
Kiss me.
什麽
What?
別什麽了 照做就行 吻我
Don't "what" me, just do it. Kiss me.
你認真的?
Are you serious?
是啊 我認真的 我之前看到你在看我屁股
Yeah, I'm serious. I saw you checking out my ass earlier.
我知道你想 吻我就行
I know you want to do it. Just kiss me.
- 沒有 - 本
- No, I wasn't. - Ben!
- 好吧 我就看了一秒 - 吻我
- Okay, for a second I did. - Kiss me.
蒂尼絲 我...
Denise, I...
你可以的 來吧
You can do it. Just go for it.
- 抱歉 抱歉 - 該死 該死
- I'm sorry! I'm sorry! - Oh, fuck! Fuck.
- 真抱歉 你沒事吧 - 沒事
- I'm so sorry. Are you okay? - I'm fine.
看見沒 我說了我們不該那麽做
See? I told you we shouldn't have done that.
那不是個好主意
It was a bad idea.
沒事 再試一次
No, no, no. Let's just try it again.
不行 我感覺好蠢 我們應該找日記
No, I feel stupid. We should look for the diary.
過來
Come here.
不賴啊
Not bad.
真的?
Really?
並不是特別好 別激動
It wasn't, like, top five or anything. Don't get excited.
不過 沒錯 還可以
But, yeah, it was okay.
等你看見肯達爾了 就朝她走過去
When you see Kendall, just walk straight up to her,
對她爺們兒些
lay some of that shit on her,
她就會被你迷住
and you're golden.
好的 謝謝
Okay. Thanks.
我想是我們沒關上
Guess we left it open.
嘿 奧基
Hey, augie.
本今晚並不想丟下你
Ben didn't want to leave you tonight.
是我的主意
It was my idea.
那有什麽區別
What difference does it make?
都已經這樣了
It's done.
該死
Oh, fuck!
來
Come on.
下面到底什麽情況
What the hell is going on down there?
沒事 一切都在控制之中
We're fine! Everything's under control!
不要啊 不要啊 不能是我的屁股
No! No, no, no, no. Fucking, no! Not my ass!
不要啊 不要啊
Oh, no, no, no, no!
我的屁股 我的屁股啊
My ass! My ass!
她在嚼我的屁股
She's gumming my ass!
天啊
Oh, my god!
卡特
Carter!
天啊 好噁心
Oh, god! Oh, it's disgusting!
卡特
Carter!
再見 賤人
Peace out, bitch!
發生什麽事了
What the hell happened?
見鬼 回樓上 回樓上
Shit. Back upstairs! Back upstairs!
快 快
Come on, come on!
快移
Move it!
這擋不住他們
That's not gonna hold them!
- 你們找到日記了嗎 - 沒 我們到處都找了
- Did you find the journal? - No! We looked everywhere!
天啊 他們來了
Oh, my god! They're coming!
夥計們 我們跳的話 或許能越過柵欄
Guys, if we jump, we might be able to clear the fence!
- 什麽 - 管它呢 跳吧
- What? - Fuck it, let's just jump!
柵欄差不多10英尺遠啊
The fence is like 10 feet away!
- 我先 - 快 快
- I'll go first! - Go, go!
好了  快 快
Okay. Go, go, go!
奧基 現在該你了
Augie, you got to go now!
快
Hurry!
不行 我恐高
I can't, I'm afraid of heights!
更怕僵屍就好了 快
Be more afraid of zombies! Go!
那是他的小鶏鶏嗎
Is that his wiener?
我們得幫忙
We got to do something.
夥計們 救我 我要掉下去了
Guys, help me! I'm falling!
抓好那個鶏巴 本
Hang on to that cock, Ben!
夥計們 快點 救我
Guys, hurry! Help me!
你在幹嘛
What are you doing?
嘿 混蛋們 過來抓我啊
Hey! Assholes! Come and get me.
快
Hurry!
要斷了
It's ripping!
他的鶏巴要斷了
His dick's ripping!
- 我拿到了 - 天啊
- I got it! - Dude!
- 我拿到了 - 藏哪了
- I got it. - Where was it?
- 內衣抽屜 - 正點
- Underwear drawer. - Classic.
快跑
Run!
鎖住
Lock it.
奧基 照明
Augie, get the lights.
沒電了
The power's out.
我們是在哪
Where the hell are we?
菲爾德夫人家
Mrs. fielder's house.
不敢相信我們竟砍了她的頭
I can't believe we just chopped her head off.
她想吃我屁股 她活該
She tried to eat my ass, augie. She deserved it.
夥計們 我們得繼續轉移 快
Guys, we got to keep moving. Come on.
卡特 去窗口查看下
Carter, check the window.
見鬼 他們到處都是
Shit, they're everywhere.
菲爾德夫人的車在車庫裏
Miss fielder's car is in the garage.
或許我們能從那裏出去 這邊
Maybe we can get out that way. This way.
那是什麽
What was that?
我覺得有什麽在這裏面
I think something's in here.
該死 是貓
Fuck, cat.
奧基
Augie?
老兄 老兄
Dude, dude.
- 奧基 - 怎麽了
- Augie. - What?
別動
Don't move.
- 你打中了嗎 - 打中了 我打中了
- Did you get it? -  I got it! I got it!
快 快 快
Come on, come on, come on!
打開車庫門
Open the garage door!
開不了啊
It won't open!
開車 本 開車
Go! Ben, go!
去他媽的
Fuck it!
天呐 那是童子軍隊長羅傑斯
Oh, my god. It's scout leader Rogers!
他看上去糟透了
He looks like shit!
我放火燒了他
I set him on fire.
- 什麽 - 他想吃我啊
- What? - He tried to eat me!
等下 你在幹嘛 別...
Wait, what are you doing? No, don't...
抱歉 兄弟
Sorry, bro!
好了 日記說他們在
All right, the diary said they're at
杜瓦街的舊娛樂中心
the old rec center on dewer street.
但願我們還來得及
Hopefully, we're not too late.
好了 我會儘快叫救援的
All right, I'll try to get help as soon as I can.
小心點就是了
Just be careful.
- 蒂尼絲 - 怎麽了
- Denise. - Yeah?
聽著 我不知道之後會怎樣
Look, I don't know what's gonna happen,
但我只想讓你知道
but I just wanted to let you know that
你是我見過的最酷的姑娘
you're one of the coolest girls I've ever met.
希望你會遇到配得上你的那個人
And, uh, I hope you meet someone that deserves you.
謝謝
Thanks.
夥計們 走吧 我們去派對那
Guys, let's go. We got to get to the party.
本 這是自殺行動
Ben, this is a suicide mission.
夥計們 他們會在兩小時內
Guys, they're gonna bomb this whole town
炸了這整個鎮
in less than two hours.
要是蒂尼絲及時聯繫到軍方了呢
What if Denise reaches the military in time?
她要是沒聯繫到呢 卡特 然後會怎樣
And what if she doesn't, Carter? Then what?
誰來救他們 員警?他們都死了
Who's gonna save them? The police? They're gone.
軍方?他們也不會來
The military? They're not coming, either.
夥計們 我們是最後的防綫
Guys, we're the last line of defense.
或許我們穿著這些制服看上去像傻瓜
And so what? Maybe we look like dorks in these uniforms.
或許我們是全校人的大笑料 那又如何
And maybe we're a big joke to everyone at school.
但今晚
But tonight,
我們要讓他們見識下什麽才是真正的童子軍
we're gonna show them what being a real scout's all about.
那麽 我們是要站這裏無動於衷
So, are we just gonna stand here with our thumbs up our asses?
還是去那裏拯救世界
Or are we gonna go out there and save the world?
好樣的 老兄
Fuck, yeah, dude.
本 講得太棒了
That was a really good speech, Ben.
謝謝 奧基
Thanks, augie.
開幹吧
Let's do it.
娛樂中心往那走
The rec center's that way.
我們先去次加油站
We're making a pit stop first.
你認真的嗎
Are you serious?
我沒一條資訊能發出去 崔弗斯
None of my text messages are going through, Travis.
別擔心 寶貝
Don't worry about that, baby.
你帶我去哪
Where are you taking me?
是個驚喜
Um, it's a surprise.
你需要被輕拍下屁屁 對嗎
You need a little spanking, don't you?
崔弗斯 搞什麽啊
Travis, what the fuck?
來
Come on.
好吧 這地方好惡
Okay, this place is disgusting.
我要給你做檢查
I need to examine you.
- 過來 - 好吧
- Get over here. - Oh, okay.
天呐 你好性感
God, you're so sexy.
謝謝
Thank you.
好了 我們現在不準備做愛
Okay, we're not about to fuck right now.
爲什麽
Why not?
因爲我們約會了只有...兩分鐘的樣子
Because we've only been dating for, like, two minutes.
口交如何
What about a blow job?
崔弗斯 我花了一個小時才找到這片口香糖
Travis, I spent an hour trying to find this piece of gum.
糟透了
Sucks.
好吧 你能幫我口交
Okay, fine. You can eat me out.
- 真的? - 真的 不謝
- Really? - Yes. You're welcome.
我在監獄時
When I'm in jail
做的第一件事是和另一個小妞說話
the first thing you do  is talk to another chick.
什麽情況
What the fuck?
嘿 變態 滾開
Hey, pervert, fuck off!
你認真的嗎 兄弟
You serious, bro?
我當時在監獄
I was in jail!
喂 你口不口啊
Hello? Are you going to do it or what?
你的嘴有點冷
Your mouth's kind of cold.
別碰
Stop.
- 別碰 - 別這樣 寶貝
- Stop! - Come on, babe.
- 住手 - 你他媽有病啊
- Stop it! - What the fuck's your problem?
我在擔心我弟
I'm worried about my brother.
他幾小時前就該到了
He should've been here hours ago.
他不會來 寶貝
He's not coming, babe.
你怎麽知道
How do you know?
我給了他錯誤的地址
Because I gave him the wrong address.
- 什麽 - 他們是童子軍 肯達爾
- What? - They're scouts, Kendall!
聽著 你覺得我真會邀請他們嗎
Look, what'd you think, i was gonna invite them for real?
- 過來 - 你真是個混蛋
- Come here. -  You are such a dick!
- 怎麽 你可不會離開 - 看著
- What? You're not leaving. - Watch me!
別想走
You're not going!
好吧 走吧 婊子
Fine, go, bitch!
天呐 姑娘 用根衛生棉條行嗎
Oh, Jesus, girl. Get a fucking tampon, would you?
來人救命啊
Someone help!
救命 拜託 來人救命
Help! Please, someone help!
好了 童子軍們 讓僵屍嘗嘗我們的厲害
All right, scouts, let's kick some zombie ass.
碰
Boom.
克洛伊?
Chloe?
釘中
Nailed it.
大混蛋
What a dick.
本 他們到處都是啊
Ben, they're everywhere!
集合
Circle up!
你們想嘗嘗這個?
You want some of this?
混蛋們 去死吧
You assholes! Die!
來啊 你們想要我的一塊肉?
Come on! You want a piece of me?
本 本
Ben! Ben!
救命
Help!
本
Ben!
堅持住 肯達爾 我來了
Hang on, Kendall! I'm coming!
見鬼
Oh, shit.
見鬼 見鬼 啓動啊 快
Oh, shit. Shit, start! Come on!
本 當心
Ben, look out!
本 閃開
Ben, duck!
本
Ben!
肯達爾 下來 爬下來 快
Kendall, come down! Climb down, hurry!
- 你沒事吧 - 我想我沒事
- Are you okay? - Yeah, I think so.
夥計們 快走
Guys, come on!
快走 快
Come on. Come on!
我們得帶所有人出去 走吧
We got to get everyone out of here! Let's go!
所有人都去樓梯那 快
Everybody! Get to the stairs! Come on!
走吧
Let's go!
快 所有人 快走
Come on, everybody, move!
快 快走 快 快走
Hurry up! Come on, come on! Let's go!
快走
Let's go!
快走 快
Let's go! Come on!
見鬼
Oh, shit!
你在幹嘛
What are you doing?
我們要是不鎖上門 他們就會跟著你們 你必須離開
They'll follow you if we don't lock the doors! You gotta go!
- 你呢 - 你必須離開 相信我
- What about you? - You got to go! Trust me!
我不要離開你 不行
I'm not leaving you! No!
快走 快走 相信我
Go! Go! Trust me!
我沒彈藥了 見鬼
I'm out! Oh, shit!
他們太多了 快走 快 快
There's too many of them! Come on, let's go! Hurry!
快走
Let's go!
可惡
Oh, fuck!
快走
Let's go!
快
Come on!
快 快走
Hurry, come on!
快走 奧吉 快
Go, augie, go!
快跑 快跑
Run! Run!
門在哪
Where's the door?
一定有另一個出口
There's got to be another exit.
我一個都沒看到
I don't see one!
- 我們被困住了 - 見鬼
- We're trapped. - Shit.
這裏沒法出去 可惡
There's no way out of here. Fuck.
怎麽辦 把你的背包給我
What do we do? Give me your backpack.
幹嘛 你在幹嘛
What? What are you doing?
- 那是什麽 - 炸彈
- What is that? - It's a bomb.
你做了顆炸彈?
You made a bomb?
你是什麽人 塔利班?
What are you, the Taliban?
我們要麽快點死 要麽被活活吃了
Either we die fast or we're eaten alive
再轉變成那些東西的一員
and turn into one of those things!
自己選吧
Your choice.
見鬼 卡特 把你的打火機給我
Shit. Carter, give me your lighter.
給
Here.
你們準備好沒
Are you guys ready?
- 等下 - 怎麽了
- Wait! - What?
我得說幾句
I need to say something.
本 沒事的
Ben, it's fine.
- 你不必這樣 - 不行 我得說
- You don't have to do this. - No, I do.
我們今晚根本不該甩開你 奧基
We should have never ditched you tonight, augie.
我們的所作所爲真的糟透了
What we did was really messed up.
他說的對 我們是徹頭徹尾的蠢貨
He's right. We've been complete d-bags.
都怪我 我絕不該讓你們認爲
It's my fault. I never should have made you guys think
你們只是因爲我而不得不留在童子軍
you had to be in scouts for just me.
就是因爲你啊
No, that's just it!
我以爲我想退出 但我就是擔心
I thought I wanted out, but I was just worried
別人會怎麽想 事實是
what other people were gonna think. The truth is,
我喜歡做童子軍
I love being a scout.
我喜歡是因爲我因此而認識你們
And I love it because it's the reason i met you guys.
我知道今晚很瘋狂 也糟透了
And I know tonight's been really crazy and fucked up,
但有一件好事
but one good thing has happened.
就是現在
And it's this, right now.
我們
Us.
又在一起了
Being back together.
童子軍萬歲
Scouts forever.
本 要是我現在牽住你的手是不是很挫?
Ben? Is it really lame if I hold your hand right now?
不會
No.
該死的 蠢東西
Oh, god damn it. This stupid thing!
- 你在幹嘛 - 沒燃油了
- What are you doing? - It's out of fluid!
拿來 給我
Here. Give me that.
等下 你有別的打火機嗎
Wait, do you have another lighter?
該死的 奧基 我們本該快點死的
God damn it, augie, we were supposed to die fast!
這下要痛死了
This is gonna hurt so bad.
快 奧基 你行的
Come on, augie, you can do it!
別給我壓力 我討厭壓力
Don't pressure me! I hate that!
嘿 白癡們 你們要在那坐著還怎麽
Yo, dipshits! You just gonna sit there or what?
她哪冒出來的
Where'd she come from?
奧基 別管它了
Augie, leave it!
奧基 走吧
Augie, let's go!
你們沒事吧
Are you guys okay?
我活著 我活著
I'm alive. I'm alive!
天呐 奧基
Oh, my god! Augie!
老兄 你是個天才 成功了
Dude! You're a genius! It worked!
太屌了
That was fucking awesome!
太好了 兄弟 成功了
Fuck, yeah, man! It worked!
什麽情況
What the fuck?
那是童子軍隊長羅傑斯嗎
Is that scout leader Rogers?
你不得不佩服他 這人很拼啊
You got to hand it to him. The man is a fighter.
見鬼 誰有武器
Oh, shit. Does anybody have a weapon?
這附近一定有能用的
There's got to be something around here.
每次都他媽這樣
Every goddamn time!
來的真是時候
Now you decide to show up.
疏散隊
Evacuation fleet
前往第二地點
moving to secondary location.
夥計 你看上去糟透了
Dude, you look like shit.
是啊 你還想怎麽樣
Yeah, well, what do you expect?
我整晚都在殺僵屍
I've been killing zombies all night.
是啊 昨晚你有點屌
Yeah, you were kind of badass last night.
謝謝回來
Well, thanks for coming back.
總得有人救你們
Somebody's got to keep saving your ass.
是啊 我想也是
Yeah, I guess so.
那麽 今後我們一起混嗎 或是...
So, um, are we gonna hang out after this, or...
拜託 我覺得我們四個現在是一隊了
Come on, I feel like the four of us are a team now.
安心點 夥計
Relax, dude.
現在你有正事要做
You've got some business to take care of right now.
去吧 你行的
Go for it. You got this.
- 好 - 去吧
-All right. -Go.
我很高興你沒事
I am so happy that you're okay.
噢  好溫馨 擊掌
Oh, that's so sweet. Up top!
老兄 我不會爲這事擊掌
Dude, I'm not high-fiving that.
拜託
Come on.
你覺得我會爲這事擊掌?
You think I'm high-fiving that?
別這樣
Come on!
看看他們啊
Aww, look at them!
你是什麽人
Who are you?
我是一名童子軍
I'm a scout.
好吧 這表示
All right, well, this just means
- 我要上了他媽 - 嘿
- I'm gonna fuck his mom. - Hey!
怎麽了
What?
拜託
Come on.
結束
The end.